he has welcome to this problem we're
going to factor this trinomial so
anytime there's a leading coefficient
that's greater than 1 I like to do it
this way so i'll make an X and I'll make
a box so 3 times 6 is 18 so when two
numbers that multiply to 18 and the 11
goes down here so we do is two numbers
multiply to 18 and add to 11 that's nine
and two so this 3x squared is going to
be written here the 6 is written down
here and then we're going to split this
11x up in 29 x + 2 X we're going to put
them here in here so now you just find
out what the outside would be to give
you this inside so put a 3x here and an
X here so 3x times x is 3x squared the
reason I chose put the 3x here is
because I want to line up with this 9x
so 3x times what is 9x that's positive 3
then x times what is 2x it's positive 2
so the final answer here is 3x plus 2
for this top one and for the side is X
plus 3 and that is the answer fully
factored if that makes sense talk to you
guys soon bye